BIBIMBAP	(Korean) a dish of rice, sautied and seasoned vegetables, and hot pepper paste [n -S]
BIBIMBAPS	BIBIMBAP, (Korean) a dish of rice, sautied and seasoned vegetables, and hot pepper paste [n]
CHAEBOL	(Korean) a group of businesses in Korea owned by one family [n -S]
CHAEBOLS	CHAEBOL, (Korean) a group of businesses in Korea owned by one family [n]
CHON	(Korean) a Korean monetary unit, also JEON [n -S]
CHONS	CHON, (Korean) a Korean monetary unit, also JEON [n]
GOCHUJANG	a spicy paste used in Korean cuisine that is made from red chili peppers, glutinous rice, and fermented soybeans [n -S]
GOCHUJANGS	GOCHUJANG, a spicy paste used in Korean cuisine that is made from red chili peppers, glutinous rice, and fermented soybeans [n]
HANGUL	(Korean) an alphabetic script for Korean [n -S]
HANGULS	HANGUL, (Korean) an alphabetic script for Korean [n]
HAPKIDO	(Japanese) a Korean martial art [n -S]
HAPKIDOS	HAPKIDO, (Japanese) a Korean martial art [n]
JEON	(Korean) a monetary unit of South Korea, also CHON [n -S]
JEONS	JEON, (Korean) a monetary unit of South Korea, also CHON [n]
JUN	a North Korean coin [n JUN]
KIMCHEE	(Korean) a spicy Korean dish of pickled cabbage, also KIMCHI [n -S]
KIMCHEES	KIMCHEE, (Korean) a spicy Korean dish of pickled cabbage, also KIMCHI [n]
KIMCHI	(Korean) a spicy Korean dish of pickled cabbage, also KIMCHEE [n -S]
KIMCHIS	KIMCHI, (Korean) a spicy Korean dish of pickled cabbage, also KIMCHEE [n]
KYE	a Korean village fund which lends for weddings, funerals etc. [n -S]
KYES	KYE, a Korean village fund which lends for weddings, funerals etc. [n]
SIJO	(Korean) a Korean verse form [n -S]
SIJOS	SIJO, (Korean) a Korean verse form [n]
SOJU	(Korean) a Korean vodka distilled from rice or sweet potato [n -S]
SOJUS	SOJU, (Korean) a Korean vodka distilled from rice or sweet potato [n]
TAEKWONDO	(Korean) a Korean martial art [n -S]
TAEKWONDOS	TAEKWONDO, (Korean) a Korean martial art [n]
