AMAKHOSI	INKHOSI, a traditional leader of a Zulu clan, also INKOSI [n]
AMAKOSI	INKOSI, a traditional leader of a Zulu clan, also INKHOSI [n]
BABALAS	(Zulu) drunk, also BABBELAS [adj]
BABBELAS	(Zulu) drunk, also BABALAS [adj]
BANSELA	(Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELA, BONSELLA, PASELA [n -S]
BANSELAS	BANSELA, (Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELA, BONSELLA, PASELA [n]
BONSELA	(Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELLA, BANSELA, PASELA [n -S]
BONSELAS	BONSELA, (Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELLA, BANSELA, PASELA [n]
BONSELLA	(Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELA, BANSELA, PASELA [n -S]
BONSELLAS	BONSELLA, (Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELA, BANSELA, PASELA [n]
COCOPAN	(Zulu) in South Africa, a wagon on a narrow gauge railway serving a mine [n -S]
COCOPANS	COCOPAN, (Zulu) in South Africa, a wagon on a narrow gauge railway serving a mine [n]
DONGA	(Zulu) a gully in a veldt [n -S]
DONGAS	DONGA, (Zulu) a gully in a veldt [n]
GOGO	(Zulu) a grandmother [n -S]
GOGOS	GOGO, (Zulu) a grandmother [n]
IMBIZO	(Zulu) a gathering of people at the request of a chieftain [n -S]
IMBIZOS	IMBIZO, (Zulu) a gathering of people at the request of a chieftain [n]
IMPALA	(Zulu) an African antelope with horns curved in the shape of a lyre [n -S]
IMPALAS	IMPALA, (Zulu) an African antelope with horns curved in the shape of a lyre [n]
IMPHEE	(Zulu) any of several southern African varieties of sorghum [n -S]
IMPHEES	IMPHEE, (Zulu) any of several southern African varieties of sorghum [n]
IMPI	(Zulu) a regiment of Zulu warriors [n IMPIS or IMPIES]
IMPIES	IMPI, (Zulu) a regiment of Zulu warriors [n]
IMPIS	IMPI, (Zulu) a regiment of Zulu warriors [n]
INDABA	(Zulu) a tribal conference in southern Africa [n -S]
INDABAS	INDABA, (Zulu) a tribal conference in southern Africa [n]
INDUNA	(Zulu) a South African tribal councillor [n -S]
INDUNAS	INDUNA, (Zulu) a South African tribal councillor [n]
INKHOSI	a traditional leader of a Zulu clan, also INKOSI [n AMAKHOSI or INKHOSIS]
INKHOSIS	INKHOSI, a traditional leader of a Zulu clan, also INKOSI [n]
INKOSI	a traditional leader of a Zulu clan, also INKHOSI [n INKOSIS or AMAKOSI]
INKOSIS	INKOSI, a traditional leader of a Zulu clan, also INKHOSI [n]
KWELA	(Zulu) a form of Zulu folk music [n -S]
KWELAS	KWELA, (Zulu) a form of Zulu folk music [n]
MABELA	(Zulu) ground kaffir corn used for making porridge [n -S]
MABELAS	MABELA, (Zulu) ground kaffir corn used for making porridge [n]
MAMBA	(Zulu) a venomous African snake [n -S]
MAMBAS	MAMBA, (Zulu) a venomous African snake [n]
MBAQANGA	(Zulu) a type of Black African urban music [n -S]
MBAQANGAS	MBAQANGA, (Zulu) a type of Black African urban music [n]
MUTI	(Zulu) a traditional medicine, associated with witch-doctors [n -S]
MUTIS	MUTI, (Zulu) a traditional medicine, associated with witch-doctors [n]
NAGANA	(Zulu) a tropical disease of cattle transmitted by tsetse fly, also NGANA [n -S]
NAGANAS	NAGANA, (Zulu) a tropical disease of cattle transmitted by tsetse fly, also NGANA [n]
NGANA	(Zulu) a tropical disease of cattle transmitted by tsetse fly, also NAGANA [n -S]
NGANAS	NGANA, (Zulu) a tropical disease of cattle transmitted by tsetse fly, also NAGANA [n]
NYALA	(Zulu) a kind of antelope, also INYALA [n -S]
NYALAS	NYALA, (Zulu) a kind of antelope, also INYALA [n]
PASELA	(Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELA, BONSELLA, BANSELA [n -S]
PASELAS	PASELA, (Zulu) a gratuity to a black South African, also BONSELA, BONSELLA, BANSELA [n]
PUKU	(Zulu) an antelope of central southern Africa, related to the waterbuck [n -S]
PUKUS	PUKU, (Zulu) an antelope of central southern Africa, related to the waterbuck [n]
SANGOMA	(Zulu) a witch-doctor [n -S]
SANGOMAS	SANGOMA, (Zulu) a witch-doctor [n]
TAHA	(Zulu) the South African weaverbird [n -S]
TAHAS	TAHA, (Zulu) the South African weaverbird [n]
TIKOLOSHE	(Zulu) in Bantu folklore, a hairy malevolent dwarflike creature with supernatural powers, also TOKOLOSHE, TOKOLOSHI [n -S]
TIKOLOSHES	TIKOLOSHE, (Zulu) in Bantu folklore, a hairy malevolent dwarflike creature with supernatural powers, also TOKOLOSHE, TOKOLOSHI [n]
TOKOLOSHE	(Zulu) in Bantu folklore, a hairy malevolent dwarflike creature with supernatural powers, also TIKOLOSHE, TOKOLOSHI [n -S]
TOKOLOSHES	TOKOLOSHE, (Zulu) in Bantu folklore, a hairy malevolent dwarflike creature with supernatural powers, also TIKOLOSHE, TOKOLOSHI [n]
TOKOLOSHI	(Zulu) in Bantu folklore, a hairy malevolent dwarflike creature with supernatural powers, also TIKOLOSHE, TOKOLOSHE [n -S]
TOKOLOSHIS	TOKOLOSHI, (Zulu) in Bantu folklore, a hairy malevolent dwarflike creature with supernatural powers, also TIKOLOSHE, TOKOLOSHE [n]
VUVUZELA	(Zulu) a plastic trumpet blown by football fans [n -S]
VUVUZELAS	VUVUZELA, (Zulu) a plastic trumpet blown by football fans [n]
ZULU	a type of two-masted fishing vessel formerly used in Scotland [n -S]
ZULUS	ZULU, a type of two-masted fishing vessel formerly used in Scotland [n]
